A Guide to the Director's Office Correspondence and Subject Files of the Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1954-1986
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Correspondence and Subject Files, 1954-1984., Extent: 13 boxes. (Box 1-13)
  - Buildings & Grounds - General, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Capital Outlay, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Chambers of Commerce, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Compliments & Complaints, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Fort, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Gift Shop, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Jamestown Award, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Jamestown Award, 1967-1968 (Box 12)
  - Jamestown Foundation Trustees, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Inquiries, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Jamestown Foundation Board of Trustees Meetings, 1972 May 14 (Box 12)
  - Jamestown Foundation Board of Trustees Meetings, 1972 Dec. 2 (Box 12)
  - Jamestown Foundation Board of Trustees Meetings, 1972 Dec. 2 (Box 12)
  - Literature, Requests for, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Mermaid Tavern, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Museums (Other), 1972 (Box 12)
  - Passes, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Pavilions, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Photographs, Requests for, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Pottery, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Promotions - Outside Jamestown Festival Park, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Publications, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Publicity - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 12)
  - Publicity - Clippings, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Publicity - Releases, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Ships, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Southern Travel Directors Council, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Special Events - General, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Special Events - Indian Festival, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Special Events - Jamestown Day, 1972 (Box 12)
  - First Assembly Day - Picnic, 1972 (Box 12)
  - First Assembly Day - Speaker, 1968 (Box 9)
  - First Assembly Day - Info, 1972 (Box 12)
  - First Assembly Day - Bio, 1972 (Box 12)
  - First Assembly Day - Text, 1972 (Box 12)
  - CORESTA/TCRC, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Teachers' Questionnaires, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Thanksgiving, First, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Tour Boat, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Virginia Travel Committees, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Visitation - Conventions, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Visitation - General, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Visitation - Special Groups, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Visitation - Statistics, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Jamestown Financial Reports, 1972 (Box 12)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission & Bicentennial Corporation Financial Report, 1973 (Box 12)
  - Advertising, 1975 (Box 13)
  - APVA, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Buildings & Grounds, 1975 (Box 13)
  - British, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Busch Gardens, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Compliments & Complaints, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Fort, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Jamestown Foundation Trustees Meeting, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Glass House, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Guidebook, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Inquiries, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Jamestown Award, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Jamestown Corp., 1975 (Box 13)
  - Jamestown Foundation Financial Reports, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
  - Jamestown Medal, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Jamestown Foundation Meeting of Boards, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Jamestown Foundation Trustees, 1975 May 10 (Box 13)
  - Jamestown Society, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Literature, Requests for, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Mermaid Tavern, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Museums, 1975 (Box 13)
  - New World Pavilion Renovation, 1975 (Box 13)
  - New World Pavilion Renovation, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Pavilions, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Passes, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Parking, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Policy, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Pottery, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Photos, Requests for, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Program, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Promotions - Outside Jamestown Festival Park, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Publicity - Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 13)
  - Publications, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Reports, 1975 (Box 13)
  - R, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Research, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Services, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Thanksgiving, First, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Ships, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Signs, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Special Events - General, 1975 (Box 13)
  - National Council of Occupational Licensing, 1975 Aug. 5 (Box 13)
  - Special Events - Indian Festival, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Special Events - Jamestown Day, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Special Events - First Assembly Day, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Special Events - First Assembly Day, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Virginia Travel Committee, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Visitation - Conventions, 1975-1976 (Box 13)
  - Visitation - General, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Visitation - Special Groups, 1975 (Box 13)
  - Visitation - Statistics, 1975 (Box 13)
- Series II: History Files, 1956-1986., Extent: 18 boxes. (Box 14-31)
  - Yorktown Bicentennial Committee Meeting
    - Minutes, 1978 Mar. 2 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1978 Feb. 9 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1978 Jan. 12 (Box 14)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Committee Meeting
    - Minutes, 1978 Dec. 2 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1978 Apr. 21 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1977 Sept. 30 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1978 Sept. 30 (Original Copies) (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1977 July 22 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1977 Apr. 15 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1977 July 22 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1976 Sept. 6 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1976 Sept. 6 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1977 Jan. 14 (2 copies) (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1976 May 19 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1974 Sept. 9 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1974 Nov. 15 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1977 Jan. 17 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1974 July 11 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1974 May 31 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1974 May 11 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1974 Apr. 12 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1974 Mar. 12 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1974 Feb. 8 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1974 Jan. 11 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1973 Nov. 5 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1973 Oct. 12 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1973 Aug. 20 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1973 June 4 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1973 Apr. 16 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1973 Apr. 4 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1973 Mar. 12 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1975 Oct. 23 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1975 May 10 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1975 Apr. 7 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1974 Dec. 7 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1975 Aug. 19 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1975 Dec. 6 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1972 Dec. 29 & 1973 Mar. 12 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1972 Nov. 27 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1972 Oct. 23 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1972 Sept. 11 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1972 Apr. 3 (Box 14)
    - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1972 Aug. 5 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1972 July 14 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1972 Feb. 7 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1971 Dec. 6 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1972 Jan. 7 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1971 Aug. 27 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1971 July 17 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1971 Sept. 17 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1971 June 11 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1971 Jan. 15 (Box 14)
    - Minutes, 1971 Jan. 7 (Box 14)
  - George Washington Bicentennial Center (Alexandria, Va.) & Western Virginia Bicentennial Information Center (Charlottesville, Va.), 1972-1981 (Box 15)
  - George Washington Bicentennial Center (Alexandria, Va.) & Western Virginia Bicentennial Information Center (Charlottesville, Va.) Blueprints, 1973-1974 (Box 16)
  - Bicentennial Council of the Original Thirteen States & Interim Report on America's Victory Celebration, 1975-1981 (Box 17)
  - Yorktown Bicentennial - Lodgings & Accommodations and Report of French Participation, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs, 1980-1982 (Box 17)
  - Preliminary Study - Museum of Frontier Culture, 1985 (Box 17)
  - America's Victory Celebration Maps, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Yorktown Bicentennial Center Administration, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Virginia 350th Anniversary Celebration Corp. - Report on Audit, 1958 (Box 17)
  - Charlottesville Bicentennial Commission, 1971-1975 (Box 17)
  - Specifications for the Western Virginia Bicentennial Information Center (Charlottesville, Va.), 1974 (Box 17)
  - America's Victory Celebration - Official Program, 1981 (Box 17)
  - America's Victory Celebration - Poster, 1981 (Box 17)
  - America's Victory Celebration - Opening Ceremony Program, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Norfolk Water Video (VHS), n.d. (Box 17)
  - Museum of Frontier Culture Cost Estimating, 1986 (Box 17)
  - Financial Reports, 1976-1982 (Box 17)
  - Financial Reports Work Papers, 1982-1983 (Box 17)
  - Asbestos Removal, n.d. (Box 17)
  - Manville Property Damage Settlement Trust, 1989 (Box 17)
  - Tax Report - American Frontier Culture Foundation, 1982-1984 (Box 17)
  - Battle of Yorktown Map Reproduction, n.d. (Box 17)
  - Financial Report of the Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission & VIBC, 1980 (Box 18)
  - Capital Outlay Forms for Yorktown Victory Center & Alexandria & Charlottesville Centers, 1973-1974 (Box 18)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation Board of Trustees Meeting, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation Financial Report, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission Report on Audit (3 copies), 1981 (Box 18)
  - Statement on Budget & Expenditures, 1979 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission Financial Report, 1978 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, Program Exhibit, Brochures, & Legislation, 1971-1982 (Box 18)
  - Cultural Laureate Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Agreements, 1974-1981 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1978 Dec. 2 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1978 Apr. 21 (Box 18)
  - Article - "Three Bicentennial Centers Open," n.d. (Box 18)
  - American Revolutionary Bicentennial by the Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies, 1974 (Box 18)
  - Budget Manual & Other Budget Workshop Materials, 1975 (Box 18)
  - Draft Letter from Lewis A. McMurran, Jr., to Governor Mills Godwin, n.d. (Box 18)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Concessionaire Agreement, 1975 (Box 18)
  - Project Completion Reports, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1975 Aug. 19 (Box 18)
  - Second Addendum to Concessionaire Agreement, 1975 (Box 18)
  - Kenbridge Construction Co., 1974 (Box 18)
  - Charlottesville - Capital Outlay - Costs, 1974-1976 (Box 18)
  - Alexandria - Capital Outlay - Funding & Budget, 1972-1974 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Financial Report, 1972 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Report on Audit, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes & Correspondence, 1966-1971 (Box 18)
  - Commissioners (Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission), 1971-1979 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Memorandums, 1975-1981 (Box 18)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Commission Members (Lists of), 1981 (Box 18)
  - Yorktown - Cost Estimates, 1974-1976 (Box 18)
  - Yorktown International Bicentennial Committee, Inc., 1981-1982 (Box 19)
  - Bicentennial Close-Out Reports, 1981-1983 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Financial Report, 1975 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Financial Report, 1976 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Financial Report, 1979 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Financial Report, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Exhibit, 1980-1982 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Budget Materials, 1967-1976 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Program Exhibit, 1982-1984 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Program Exhibit, 1980-1982 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1979 July 6 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Promotion Report, 1980 (Box 19)
  - Report to Commission, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Moving & Relocation Regulations, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Audit Report, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Audit Report, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Articles of Incorporation of the Cultural Laureate Foundation, 1972 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Minutes, 1978 Dec. 2 (Box 19)
  - Cultural Laureate Awards, 1976 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence, Statements of Budgets & Expenditures, Memos, etc. (loose), 1974-1981 (Box 19)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation Financial Report (2 copies), 1981 (Box 19)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation Expenditures, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Vermont Bicentennial Commission Letter, 1974 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence, Cultural Laureate Foundation, Brochures, Congressional Record, Cultural Laureate Awards, etc. (loose), 1974 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 19)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Daily change Account Funds, 1978 (Box 19)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Concessionaire Agreement, 1981 (Box 19)
  - Erosion & Sediment Control Law, 1977 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Federal City Council, 1969-1973 (Box 20)
  - General Correspondence
    - 1976 (Box 20)
    - 1977-1979 (Box 20)
  - Funds, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Fireworks, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Filmn Requests, 1973-1975 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - General Correspondence, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Council of Churches, 1974-1975 (Box 20)
  - Cultural Laureate, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Cyclorama, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Environment, 1980-1981 (Box 20)
  - Ferry Farm - Projects, 1971-1973 (Box 20)
  - Bicentennial Council of the Original Thirteen States, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Projects - British Student Exchange, 1974-1976 (Box 20)
  - Patricia Burton (America's Frontier, Ltd.), 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - Churches, 1976 (Box 20)
  - "Community Leaders" American Biographical Society, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Contributors, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Projects - Convocation - Colonial Colleges, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Cookbook, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Bicentennial Information Network (BINET), 1973-1974 (Box 20)
  - American Issues Forum, ca. 1975 (Box 20)
  - American Issues Forum - Leader Kit, 1975 (Box 20)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Museum Program Guidelines, 1976 (Box 20)
  - National Endowment for the Arts American Issues Forum, 1974 (Box 20)
  - National Endowment for the Arts American Issues Forum - Report on Implementation of the Forum, 1974 (Box 20)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Participation in the American Issues Forum, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Belgium, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Bells, 1973-1975 (Box 20)
  - Bible Society, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Bicentennial Committee for Educational Projects (BICEP), 1975 (Box 20)
  - American Issues Forum, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Associated Organizations, 1976-1977 (Box 20)
  - Associated Organizations, 1975-1976 (Box 20)
  - Associated Organizations - Arts & Humanities, 1974-1975 (Box 20)
  - Associated Organizations - Fifth Planning District, n.d. (Box 20)
  - Commission (Roanoke), 1974 (Box 20)
  - Associated Organizations - U.S. Travel Service, 1974 (Box 20)
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Administration (ARBA) - Meeting House, 1973-1975 (Box 20)
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Administration (ARBA) - Miscellaneous Locales, 1973-1975 (Box 20)
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Administration (ARBA) - Washington, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
  - Bicentennial Council of the Original Thirteen States (BCTOS), 1973-1981 (Box 20)
  - Account Book, 1974-1976 (Box 21)
  - Advertising, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Advertising, 1976 (Box 21)
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Administration (ARBA), 1976 (Box 21)
  - Alexandria Bicentennial Center, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Antiques Forum, 1976 (Box 21)
  - APVA, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Archaeology, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Yorktown Attendance Record, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Bacon's Rebellion, 1974-1976 (Box 21)
  - Bermuda Trip, 1975-1976 (Box 21)
  - Bicentennial - General, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Bicentennial - Celebration, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Bicentennial Council of the Original Thirteen States (BCTOS), 1976 (Box 21)
  - Buildings & Grounds, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Bikecentennial, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Colonial Williamsburg - Correspondence, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Compliments & Complaints, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Compliments & Complaints, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Cultural Laureate Center, 1975-1976 (Box 21)
  - Bicentennial Debates, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Exhibits, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Exhibits, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Financial Reports, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Fort, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Funds, 1976 (Box 21)
  - General Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 21)
  - Yorktown Victory Center, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Opening, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Inquiries, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Jamestown Foundation - Job Inquiries, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Literature, Requests for, 1976 (Box 21)
  - McDonald's Tree Planting - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Mermaid Tavern, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Mt. Vernon Sound & Light, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Movement of Marker in London, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Newsletter, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Outside Usage, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Passes, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Photos, Requests for, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Gift Shop, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Yorktown Victory Center, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Gift Shop, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Hot Air Balloon Assoc., 1975-1976 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Visitations, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Special Events - Writ of Quo Warranto, 1974-1976 (Box 21)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - General Correspondence, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Western Virginia Bicentennial Center, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Bicentennial "Salute to the French," 1976 (Box 21)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - First National Bank of Yorktown Agreement, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Bicentennial Publications, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Requests for Governor Darden's Speech, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Publications, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Publicity for Jamestown Foundation, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Research, 1967-1973 (Box 21)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Restaurant, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Scotch-Irish Symposium, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Ships, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Signs, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Special Events - General, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Virginia State Fair, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Status Reports, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Underwater Exploration - York River, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Seal, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Time Capsule, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Visitation - Conventions, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Local Commissions, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Visitation - General, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Visitation - Special, 1976 (Box 21)
  - De Grasse Program, 1975-1977 (Box 21)
  - Bicentennial Map, 1976-1977 (Box 21)
  - Bettie J. Matthews Files (Coordinator of Special Events) (Correspondence, Memos, Lists, Press Releases, Itinerary, Invitation Forms, Printed Material, Photographs, Publications, News Clippings, Bikecentennial Information) (loose), 1975-1980 (Box 22)
  - Bettie J. Matthews Files (Coordinator of Special Events) (Correspondence, Press Releases, Itinerary, Articles, Time Capsule Information, Operation Plans) (loose), 1976-1981 (Box 23)
  - Conference for Social Studies Educators (Charlottesville), 1976-1981 (Box 23)
  - Charlottesville - Operation of Center, 1977 (Box 23)
  - Charlottesville - Newspaper Clippings, 1976 (Box 23)
  - Charlottesville - Opening of Center, 1974-1976 (Box 23)
  - Mellon - Project, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
  - Charlottesville - Personnel, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
  - Charlottesville - Visitation, 1975-1982 (Box 23)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Pre-Planning Study, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation Statements of Cash Receipts & Disbursements, 1985 (Box 23)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation Marketing & Promotions Dept., 1986 (Box 23)
  - Conference for Scotch-Irish Studies, 1976 (Box 24)
  - First Assembly Day - Operation Plan, 1975-1978 (Box 24)
  - First Assembly Day - News Releases, 1977 (Box 24)
  - First Assembly Day - General, 1977 (Box 24)
  - First Assembly Day - TAC Band & Chorus, 1976-1977 (Box 24)
  - First Assembly Day - Program Participants, 1976-1977 (Box 24)
  - First Assembly Day, 1976 (Box 24)
  - First Assembly Day - Rev. Robert Hunt, 1956 & 1976 (Box 24)
  - First Assembly Day - Programs, 1977 (Box 24)
  - First Assembly Day - Invitations & Mailing List, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Publications, 1976 (Box 24)
  - First Assembly Day - Room Reservations, 1971, 1976-1977 (Box 24)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - General Correspondence, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Exhibits, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Exhibits, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Compliments & Complaints, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Compliments & Complaints, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Newsletter Information, 1979-1980 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Newsletter, 1978-1980 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Promotions, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Park Rouse - Personal Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 24)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Inquiries, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Leslie Schultz (International Trade & Transportation Counselor), 1977 (Box 24)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Gift Shop, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Inquiries, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - General, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Advertising, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Alexandria Bicentennial Center, 1977 (Box 24)
  - APVA, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Bicentennial Council of the Original Thirteen States (BCTOS), 1977 (Box 24)
  - Bicentennial Debates, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Bicentennial - General, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Meeting, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Restaurant, 1978 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Promotions, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Gift Shop, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Job Inquiries, 1976-1977 (Box 24)
  - Mermaid Tavern, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Job Inquiries, 1976-1977 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Newsletter, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Photo Requests, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Press Releases, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Promotions, 1977-1978 (Box 24)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Restaurant, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Ships, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Special Events, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Jamestown Festival Park & Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission Publication Information, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Virginia Independence Bicentennial Commission - Publication Time Capsule, 1977 (Box 24)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Visitations, 1976-1977 (Box 24)
  - Western Virginia Bicentennial Center, 1977 (Box 24)
  - First Assembly Day - News Releases, 1978 (Box 25)
  - First Assembly Day - Attendees Check List, 1978 (Box 25)
  - First Assembly Day - Operations Plan, 1978 (Box 25)
  - First Assembly Day - Room Reservations, 1978 (Box 25)
  - First Assembly Day - General, 1978 (Box 25)
  - First Assembly Day - Program Participants, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Jamestown Festival Park & Yorktown Victory Center Publications Information, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Visitations, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Jamestown Festival Park - Special Events, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Western Virginia Bicentennial Center, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Yorktown Victory Center - Special Events, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Bicentennial Debates, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Alexandria Bicentennial Center, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Bicentennial Council of the Original Thirteen States (BCTOS), 1978 (Box 25)
  - Bicentennial - General, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1978 (Box 25)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1978 (Box 25)